Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 3: Boxes 45-66
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 3: Boxes 45-66
- Box: 66, Folder: 9 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: Hercules Mixer January-February 1949, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
    By Hercules Powder. Articles: "Hercules in 1948" and "Where Hercules Income Went in 1948". Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Hercules Mixer January-February 1950, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
    By Hercules Powder. Articles: "Hercules in 1949," "Where Hercules Income Went in 1949," and "Hercules Looks at 1950". Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Hercules Mixer January-February 1951, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: The Rocket Vol. 5 No. 16, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
    By Hercules Powder. July 31. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Rocket Vol. 5 No. 15, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
    By Hercules Powder. July 24. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Beacon Rocket Vol. 8 No. 48, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
    By Hercules Powder. February 8. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Hercules Mixer December 1946, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
    By Hercules Powder. Article: "Safety Then and Now: 1902-1946". Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Application Blan, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Item 14: Hercules Mixer May 1947, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
    By Hercules Powder. Articles: "Pittsburgh People," "18,966 weeks of Vacation," World's Biggest Printer". Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Documentary Material on File at the Industrial Relations Section Hercules Powder, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Item 16: Memorandum on Industrial Relations Activities (Confidential), Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
    By Hercules Powder. Filled questionnaire by Hercules. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Checklist of Material Needed On Company Industrial Relations Activities, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
    By Hercules Powder. Includes insert: "Documentary Matieral on File at the Industrial Relations Section". Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Documentary Matrial on File at the Industrial Matieral Section: Hercules Powder, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Item 19: Checklist of Material Needed On Company: Hercules Powder, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
    By Hercules Powder. February 24. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Let's Win: the National Safety Council's Safety Contest: work together for SAFETY, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
    By Hercules Powder. Poster. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: How're We Doin'? 27 Plant Injuries In First 4 Months This Year!, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Item 22: Stock ownership, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
    By Hercules Powder. May 9, " this plan has been favorably received by the employes, and on December 31, 1924, this Company had a total of 3880 stockholders, of whom 25.67 per cent are employes.". Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Attention: Mr. J. Douglas Brown, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
    By Hercules Powder. Semptember 20 Answers to questions concerning stocks. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Agreement, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
    By Hercules Powder. April 10, between Hercules Powder and Union Local No. 364. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Hercules Mizer January, 1931, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
    By J. N. Dorsey. Article: "The Dispensary at Union Plant". Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Working With Hercules, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Item 27: The Hercules Digester February 11, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
    By Hercules Powder. Article" "Union Mass Meeting Vetoes Strik; Contract Will Be Signed Next Week". Item is in English.
  - Item 28: The Hercules Mixer vo. 25 no. 3 (March), Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Item 29: Hercules Mixer October 1944, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
    By Hercules Powder. Article: "Radford Women Now Have Own Counselor". Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Hercules Mixer January-February 1950, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
    By Helen C. Kelly. The History of Our Experiment Station. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Hercules Mixer December 1946, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
    By Hercules Powder. Article: "News About Hercules". Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Hercules Mixer May, 1946, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
    By Hercules Powder. Article: "Longer Vacations For Long-Service Herculites". Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Hercules Mixer July-August 1950, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
    By Hercules Powder. Articles: "An Anniversary Message from C.M. Rutteman," N.V. Hercules Powder,". Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Employment Procedures, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
    By Hercules Powder. Includes: application forms, application index card, service record card, salary card, personnel record card, personnel questionnaire, employe rating report with instructions sheet, recruting publication, salary roll transfor or left employ form. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Medical Program, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Item 36: Annual Examinations, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Item 37: Report of Interview Mr. J. Hourihan, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
    By Helen Baker. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Accident & Health Data, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Item 39: Benefits and services For Hercules Salaried Employes, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Item 40: Excerpt from letter from John S. Shaw, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Item 41: Personnel record, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Item 42: Letter on Leave of Absence, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Item 43: Leave of Absence War Labor Policies, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Item 44: Industrial Relations Section Princeton University, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Item 45: Report of Interview of Mr. J Hourihan, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Item 46: Value of Group Insurance Plans Demonstrated, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
    By Hercules Mixer. Item is in English.
  - Item 47: Plan was inaugurated, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Item 48: To the Employes of The Hercules Powderr Co., Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Item 49: Letter about educational refund plan to Mr J. Douglas Brown, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Item 50: Women in Industry Letter to Mr John Hourihan, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Item 51: Jobs With a Future At Hercules, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Item 52: Accident Statistics, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Item 53: Accident Statistics 2, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Item 54: Industrial Injuries, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Item 55: Hercules Motor Vehicle Accidents, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Item 56: Industrial Injuries April 1942, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Item 57: Industrial Injuries June, 1947, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Item 58: You and Your Job At Hercules, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Item 59: Employe Rating Report, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Item 60: Hercules Careers Mechanical and electrical and civil engineers, Publication (Box 66, Folder 9)
- Box: 66, Folder: 10 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Hercules Careers, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Think of Tomorrow's Opportunities Today In The Field of Explosives Sales Engineering with Hercules Powder, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
    By Hercules Powder. For mining engineers, civil engineers geologists, petroleum engineers, and geological engineers. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Room For Growth For Mechanical Civil Electrical Engineers at Hercules, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Careers with Hercules: Chemical materials for industry, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: How the Hercules Medical Department can help you to keep healthy, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: This New Program of Extended Health Benefits is offered for First Time in Delaware to the employees of the Hercules Powder, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
    By Hercules Powder. October 28 preface letter by the managing director of Blue Cross Blue Shield of Delaware. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: For National Security Keep Your Country's and Your Company's Secrets, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
    By Hercules Powder. Employes are asked to read this memorandum and keep it handy for ready reference. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Instructions For Clerical Progress Sheet, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
    By Hercules Powder. Evaluation form included. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Hercules Powder Parlin Plant Progress Rating Report Supervisory -- Technical, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
    By Hercules Powder. January 11; evaluation form attached. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Instructions For Hercules Employee Performance Sheet, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Item 11: WELCOME Enclosed are a few items that will help you start your new career with Hercules, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
    By Hercules Powder. Empty folder. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Personnel Record Forms, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
    By Hercules Powder. Forms attached. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: What Is Hercules?, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Item 14: What Is Hercules?, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Item 15: Careers with Hercules: Chemical Materials For Industry, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
    By Hercules Powder. Careers with Hercules. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Careers With Hercules, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Item 17: Motor Vehicle Accidents - Second Quarter - 1947, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Item 18: Safety Bulletins for 1948, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
    By John S. Shaw. Booklet of a year's worth of Safety Bulletins. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Benefits and Services For Hercules Wage-Roll Employes, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Item 20: Scale For Scientific Technical Staff, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
    By Hercules Powder. Rubric. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Medical Program, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
    By Hercules Powder. May 22. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Salary Allotment Insurance Plan Thirteenth Edition, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
    By Hercules Powder. Effective January 1, 1942. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Group Accident And Sickness Insurance Plan Fourth Edition, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Item 24: Vacation Plan, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Item 25: Absences Continuing Into The Month of, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
    By Hercules Powder. This form is designed to obtain information, for the Medical Deparment records, concerning absences caused by illnes or injury. All absences of one or more days which terminate in the current period, should be reported on this form. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Hercules Powder Statement of Tabulable Industrial Injuries Operation Plants, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
    By Hercules Powder. January 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Salary Roll - Left Employ Or Leave Of Absence, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Item 28: Application For Employment, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Item 29: Employe Rating Report, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Item 30: Merit Rating, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Item 31: The Parlin Plan Of Supervisory Training Hercules Powder Parlin, New Jersey, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Item 32: Hercules Mixer January 1947, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
    By Hercules Powder. Articles: It's even better [new insurance policy]; Sources & Uses of Principal Hercules Products; Yeare End Review; Plant Engineers Meet; New Insecticide Poison. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Hercules Mixer April, 1947, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
    By Hercules Powder. Article: at your Service. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Hercules Mixer June, 1947, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
    By Hercules Powder. Article: An ansewr to Juveinle Delinquency from Hercules Plant. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Hercules Mixer, July-Agust 1947, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
    By Hercules Powder. Article: There is a Doctor In The House. Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Hercules Mixer September, 1947, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
    By Hercules Powder. Article: HERCULES is proud. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Hercules Mixer January-February 1952, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
    By Hercules Powder. Articles: The National 4-H Club; Hercules Looks At 1951;Where Hercules Income Went in 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Hercules Mixer January-February 1953, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
    By Hercules Powder. Articles: From Our Company's Annual Report. Item is in English.
  - Item 39: Motor Vehicle Accidents 1948, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
    By John S. Shaw. Pamphlets for first three quarters of 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Hercules Mixer July-Agust 1951, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
    By Hercules Powder. Article: Safety Pays Off. Item is in English.
  - Item 41: The Hercules Mixer September-October, 1949, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
    By Hercules Powder. Vol. XXXI, No. 5; Article: The Hercules Library. Item is in English.
  - Item 42: Hercules Mixer May-June, 1950, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
    By Hercules Powder. Article: Hercules Pension Plan Improved - Three Important Changes in Our Pension Plan Announced by the Board of Directors. Item is in English.
  - Item 43: Hercules Mixer September-October 1950, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
    By Hercules Powder. Article: Hercules Announces A New and Liberal Group Life Insurance Plan. Item is in English.
  - Item 44: The Hercules Mixer July-August, 1953, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
    By Hercules Powder. Vil. XXXV No. 4; Article: New Insurance Plan Goes Into Effect. Item is in English.
  - Item 45: Hercules Mixer May-June 1949, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
    By Hercules Powder. Article: An Extra Vacation Divident for Herculites. Item is in English.
  - Item 46: Hercules Mixer November 1948, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
    By Hercules Powder. Article:Mansfield Has the Neighbors In - Open house for employes, their families, and the neighbors attracts big crowds. Item is in English.
  - Item 47: Hercules Mixer September, 1948, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
    By Hercules Powder. To Protect Your Health. Item is in English.
  - Item 48: Enjoy Your Vacation -- Driev Safely, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
    By Hercules Powder. Pin-up (?). Item is in English.
  - Item 49: Treat Every Electric Wire As "Alive" Until You Know It Is "Dead", Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Item 50: Make Today Safe - Use More Care, Publication (Box 66, Folder 10)